Naqiyatun Muallifah

Palembang, Indonesia | 0887 0642 9228 | naqiyatunmf@gmail.com | https://porto-nq.vercel.app

SUMMARY

I am an experienced Frontend Developer with a strong passion for learning. I have honed my skills especially in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Next Js, enabling me to transform design concepts into functional and responsive web applications. I have a keen eye for detail and am dedicated to optimizing the user experience through clean and efficient code.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Dinas Komunikasi dan Informatika Kota Palembang

Oct 2022 - Now

Web Programmer

- Build, develop, and maintain web-based applications
- Translate user or client needs into functional frontend design using Next Js, MUI and SASS
- Work in a team with UI/UX Designer and Backend Developer
- Live products:

https://satudata.palembang.go.id, https://kec-plaju.palembang.go.id, https://diskopukm.palembang.go.id, https://sanjo.palembang.go.id, https://damkar.palembang.go.id, https://bakohumas.palembang.go.id, etc

PT. Estetico Fournir Agung - Palembang

Jun 2022 - Sept 2022

Frontend Developer

- Created inventory management and e-commerce webs using React Js and Tailwind
- Made custom UI based on user needs via e-commerce platform (Lightspeed) with CSS, JavaScript, JQuery
- Worked in a team with UI/UX Designer and Backend Developer

INTERNSHIP

PT. Lingkaran Sistem Intelektual - Palembang

Dec 2021 - Mar 2022

Frontend Developer

- Created a website that sells website templates using Bootstrap 5 and SASS
- Worked in a team with Database Engineers and a Backend Developer
- Learned about Agile software development methodologies (Scrum)

Meteorological Stations - Meteorological, Climatological and Geophysical Agency, Palembang

Jul 2020

- Learned mapping using QGIS
- Learned about weather parameter gauges
- Processed and analyzed the distribution of hotspots in South Sumatra for the last 5 years, checked the correlation of hotspots with weather parameters such as temperature, humidity and rainfall

EDUCATION

SRIWIJAYA UNIVERSITY - North Indralaya, South Sumatra

Aug 2017 - Dec 2021

Bachelor of Science, Major in Physics

Minors in Electronics, Instrumentation, and Computing

GPA: 3.50/4.00

My thesis or final project built a telemetry-based rainfall measuring system using the WeMos D1 mini and the SIM900A module. Rainfall data will be displayed on the website. The system is equipped with a microSD card data logger and uses PLTS to meet power requirements independently. The microcontroller is programmed using C++ technology. The website is built using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP 8, and MySQL.

Electronics and Instrumentation Laboratory - Faculty of Math and Natural Science, Sriwijaya University

Jan 2020 - May 2021

Laboratory Assistant of Analog Electronics Practicum and Digital Electronics Practicum for Physics students, Laboratory Assistant of Basic Electronics Practicum for Marine Science students

- Taught ± 50 practicum participants for each class
- Guided practicum participants to know the basic components of analog and digital electronics, how to test and calibrate electronic tools such as multimeter, oscilloscope, etc, and how to make electronic circuits on the breadboard
- Coordinated with the head of laboratory to maintain laboratory equipment
- Examined and assessed the reports of practicum participants

University Da'wah Institute - Sriwijaya University

Aug - Nov 2019

Trainer of Islamic Religious Assistance

- Taught 10 participants who were divided by the institute
- Gave 'tahsin' and 'non tahsin' materials according to the guide book
- Helped supervise exams and corrected exam results

Muslim Scientist Community (KOSMIC) - Faculty of Math and Natural Science, Sriwijaya University

Nov 2018 - Nov 2019

Treasurer of the Entrepreneurship Division

- Managed the income and expenditure of entrepreneurship funds and coordinated with the general treasurer
- Provided KOSMIC attributes such as jackets and keychains to 135 members who were interested
- Contributed to entrepreneurship such as making and selling flower bouquets during the graduation ceremony

Physics Department - Faculty of Math and Natural Science, Sriwijaya University

Aug 2018 - May 2019

Assistant Lecturer of Basic Physics I and Basic Physics II for Physics students

- Taught ± 15 participants who were divided by lecturer to improve their grades
- Gave materials and discussed questions according to the lecturer's handbook
- Helped supervise exams and corrected exam results

Faculty of Math and Natural Science - Sriwijaya University

May - Aug 2018

Treasurer of new students registration and campus life introduction activities

- Managed the income and expenditure of funds
- Guided new students in registration and provided attributes of campus life introduction activities such as 'tanjak', pin, and tie
- Helped the faculty prepare the needs such as banners, medicines, dancers, etc

ACHIEVEMENT

2021
2020
2020
-

SKILL

- Understand HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, JQuery, React Js, Next Js, Bootstrap, Tailwind, PHP, MySQL, Git/Github/Gitlab, REST API
- Embedded System (Microcontroller)
- Corel Draw, Canva
- Able to work in a team or individually